Guide to the Richard Marshall Collection of Gay Erotica and Pornography MSS.498
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series VIII. Web Fiction, 1986-2003, undated; 7 Linear Feet in 7 record cartons.; 3 electronic discs (cd-rom)
  - Frank's Boys **Friday Night** (Part 1), Unknown, Undated; cuid24437 (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - Frat Basement (Part 5), RimPigfl, 2002, cuid24438 (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Frat Boy Master, S C, 1999, cuid24439 (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - Frathouse Visitor (Parts 1, 2), Roderick Shafton, 2001; cuid24440 (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - Fucked By a Pro, Bill Drake, 2001, cuid24441 (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - Fucked Up (Parts 1-3,6,7), Roarr201, 1999; cuid24442 (Box 22, Folder 33)
  - Fuckin Around With Brother and Dad (Part 1), Anthony Jamieson, 2000; cuid24443 (Box 22, Folder 34)
  - Furface Fantasy, Galen, 1991, cuid24444 (Box 22, Folder 35)
  - Gang Bang, donaldelliot11, 1999, cuid24445 (Box 22, Folder 36)
  - Gang Banging Mario Lopez #3, Vraxis, 2001; cuid24446 (Box 22, Folder 37)
  - Garage Buddies, Mike, 2000; cuid24447 (Box 22, Folder 38)
  - The Gardner (Part 5A, 5B), Twinkie The Kid, 2000, cuid24448 (Box 22, Folder 39)
  - Gaston's Toilet, loopy, 1998, cuid24449 (Box 22, Folder 40)
  - General DIscharge, Happenstance, Undated; cuid24450 (Box 22, Folder 41)
  - Get A Grip: Hunter Men 02, Marc Tremaine, 2000, cuid24451 (Box 22, Folder 42)
  - Getting It From The Big Boys Fantasy Stud Fucking (Parts 1-3), Joe Webster, 1999; cuid24452 (Box 22, Folder 43)
  - Gimmie A Ride, Cowboy, Rimpigfl, 2003, cuid24453 (Box 22, Folder 44)
  - Gio, Hapenstance, 1998, cuid24454 (Box 22, Folder 45)
  - Glory Hole Dangers, spike4me, 2000, cuid24455 (Box 22, Folder 46)
  - Glory Hole Employment (Part 1, 2), Goo Gobbler, 2002-2003; cuid24456 (Box 22, Folder 47)
  - Glory Queen 21: The Hunting Trip, Grtbttm2, 1999; cuid24457 (Box 22, Folder 48)
  - Glory, Sparta, 1995, cuid24458 (Box 22, Folder 49)
  - Gloryhole (Chapter 1), Unknown, Undated; cuid24459 (Box 22, Folder 50)
  - Gloryhole III, Unknown, 1997; cuid24460 (Box 22, Folder 51)
  - Go West Young Man 5, Nicholas Romanov, 1998; cuid24461 (Box 22, Folder 52)
  - Gone Fishin', R. Keith Peck, 1996, cuid24462 (Box 22, Folder 53)
  - Gotta Have It (Parts 1, 2), Rim4You, 2001; cuid24463 (Box 22, Folder 54)
  - The Greece Monkey (Part 1), Shaggy, 2002, cuid24464 (Box 22, Folder 55)
  - The Green Light (Part 1), Joe Peters, 1997, cuid24465 (Box 22, Folder 56)
  - Gringo, Nathan Harvey, 1999, cuid24466 (Box 22, Folder 57)
  - The Groundskeeper, Warren Piece, 1997, cuid24467 (Box 22, Folder 58)
  - Gym Fuck, Unknown, Undated; cuid24468 (Box 22, Folder 59)
  - Gym Routine, Piano Guy, 1998, cuid24469 (Box 22, Folder 60)
  - Gym Slave, Al if you like it, 1999, cuid24470 (Box 22, Folder 61)
  - Hairy Four Fuck, Jackson Smith, 2000, cuid24471 (Box 22, Folder 62)
  - Hairy Wonder, David L. Hass, 2000, cuid24472 (Box 22, Folder 63)
  - Hakim and His Dad-3, Aaron Hernan, 2000, cuid24473 (Box 22, Folder 64)
  - Halstead: Welcome, Twenty Bucks, 2003, cuid24474 (Box 22, Folder 65)
  - Handy Man Special, an143969, 1995, cuid24475 (Box 22, Folder 66)
  - Hard Hat Area: This is a Watersports Story, Tom, 1999; cuid24476 (Box 22, Folder 67)
  - Harder, Ram Me Harder; The Adventures of Dan'te & Uncle Bud, Jim Deerboy; A. Gordon Dan'te, 1996; cuid24477 (Box 22, Folder 68)
  - Hardon Family 03: Park Patrol & Hardon Family 05: Convention Surprise, Marc Tremaine, 1998; cuid24478 (Box 22, Folder 69)
  - Hardon High 03: Head Coach, Tremaine, 1998, cuid24479 (Box 22, Folder 70)
  - Have a Look at Manlover, Unknown, Undated; cuid24480 (Box 22, Folder 71)
  - Have Balls Will Travel, Twenty Bucks, 2000, cuid24481 (Box 22, Folder 72)
  - The Hazing (Parts 8-9, 12-13), maipenraikhap, 1999, cuid24482 (Box 22, Folder 73)
  - The Head Chef (Part 2), Twinkie The Kid, 2000, cuid24483 (Box 22, Folder 74)
  - A Hell of a Price to Pay, Diesel Sniffer, 2002, cuid24484 (Box 22, Folder 75)
  - Hellbent-for-Leatherneck; Jarhead Stud; Camp Wad; Pig for Cock; PFC Check-In; Devil Dog Pupps, Devil Dog; CLayBoY, 1999; cuid24485 (Box 22, Folder 76)
  - Here Comes the Son, Unknown, Undated; cuid24486 (Box 22, Folder 77)
  - Highgate Prison, Alex J, 2000, cuid24487 (Box 22, Folder 78)
  - Highway Patrol (Part 1), An143969, 1995; cuid24488 (Box 22, Folder 79)
  - Hippie Boy Raunch, BobZuma, 1995, cuid24489 (Box 22, Folder 80)
  - Hiram, Roderick Shafton, 2000, cuid24490 (Box 22, Folder 81)
  - His Pimp, Roderick Shafton, 2000, cuid24491 (Box 22, Folder 82)
  - Holding Cell, Bawdy Pen, 2003, cuid24492 (Box 22, Folder 83)
  - Honeyboy, Eric Smith, 2001, cuid24493 (Box 22, Folder 84)
  - Horny Guy Tails #1, Eat Me!, 1995, cuid24494 (Box 22, Folder 85)
  - Horny Guy Tails From Minnesota, An106131, 1994; cuid24495 (Box 22, Folder 86)
  - Horny Guy Tails from Minnesota (#13), Unknown, 1994; cuid24496 (Box 22, Folder 87)
  - Horny Truckers, Christian, Undated; cuid24497 (Box 22, Folder 88)
  - Horse Diary (Part 2), Paulo Richart, 1995, cuid24498 (Box 22, Folder 89)
  - Hot Daddy, Agr13yoTop, 1998; cuid24499 (Box 22, Folder 90)
  - Hot Daddy, Harry, 1998, cuid24500 (Box 22, Folder 91)
  - Hot for Uncle Jeff (Part 9), Rim4you, 2000; cuid24501 (Box 22, Folder 92)
  - Hot For Uncle Jeff (Parts 14-16), Rim4You, 2000; cuid24502 (Box 22, Folder 93)
  - Hot Jock, Unknown, Undated; cuid24503 (Box 22, Folder 94)
  - Hot Jocks (Parts 1-3), Flt2, 1996; cuid24504 (Box 22, Folder 95)
  - Hot Shower, Bear Hunter, 1986, cuid24505 (Box 22, Folder 96)
  - Hotel Construction Workers, Rri610, 1996; cuid24506 (Box 22, Folder 97)
  - The House of Hell (Part 5), Phill, 1999, cuid24507 (Box 22, Folder 98)
  - House of Incest (Part 3), Unknown, 1999; cuid24508 (Box 22, Folder 99)
  - How I Became a Closet Queer (Chapters 1, 2), U4orcedme, 2000; cuid24509 (Box 22, Folder 100)
  - How I Became A Queer, Vincenzo, 2000, cuid24510 (Box 22, Folder 101)
  - The Hunter (Part 1), Joe Law, 1999, cuid24511 (Box 22, Folder 102)
  - The Hunter Men 01: Take That! General Motors, Marc Tremaine, 1999; cuid24512 (Box 22, Folder 103)
  - The Hunting Lodge, Edward08, 1999; cuid24513 (Box 22, Folder 104)
  - Hypno-Therapist, maipenraikhap, 2000, cuid24514 (Box 22, Folder 105)
  - I Can't Get Enough of Mom's Boyfriend, Kevin East Bay, 2001, cuid24515 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - I Dream of Man-Pussy; Campus Cruise, Man Lover, 1997; cuid24516 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - I Learn to Take It (Chapters 1-10), Joe Law, 1999-2000; cuid24517 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - I Learn to Take It (Chapters 11-16, 18-26), Joe Law, 1999-2000; cuid24518 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - I Sucked My Father's Cock, Local Boy, Undated; cuid24519 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - I Want You To Fuck Me, Vivek Kumar, 2000; cuid24520 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - I was Manolo's Toilet; Bobby was the Boss (Parts 1, 2), Arablover, 2002; cuid24521 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - I was Manolo's Toilet, Arablover; Joe, Tony, and Ted, Micfriend; Nick and Danny, Loopy; Open Up, Unknown, Undated; cuid24522 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - I'm A Slut for Daddy Dick, Unknown, 2001; cuid24523 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - In the Dark, Jamie Anderson, 2000, cuid24524 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Indecent Arrangement, Phoenixfr, 1998, cuid24525 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Irrigating Alabama, Jason Roberts, 1999, cuid24526 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - The Italian and the Spade, Edward Bangor, 1999, cuid24527 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Italian Dad - Part II, MosseyCJ, 2000, cuid24528 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - The Itch, and The Itch (part IV), Glaucon55, 1995; cuid24529 (Box 23, Folder 15-16)
  - The J Tape, Jake Enright, 1999, cuid24530 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Jack and Me, Botpuppy, 2000, cuid24531 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Jack the Jock, Scathole, Undated; cuid24532 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Jack Wants to Feed, Big Jack, Undated; cuid24533 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Jackin' Off My Dad When He Was Drunk & Asleep, capataur, 2003; cuid24534 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Jake's Study Hall, Glaucon55, 1998; cuid24535 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Jared Feeds, Slick, 1997, cuid24536 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Jarhead Perversion, Devil Dog, 2000, cuid24537 (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Jarhead Stud, Devil Dog, 1999, cuid24538 (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Jason and the Cop, Jason P, 2001, cuid24539 (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Jerker's Weekend Out (Parts 1-4), Phill, 1999, cuid24540 (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - Jim and His Uncle, Andy Anderson, 2002, cuid24541 (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - Jock Fever, Marc, 2001, cuid24542 (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - Jock Sex Slave (Parts 2-4), perseus, 1997-1998; cuid24543 (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - Jocksucker (Chapter 2), John Clark, 1998, cuid24544 (Box 23, Folder 31)
  - Joe, Tony and Ted, Micfriend, Undated; cuid24545 (Box 23, Folder 32)
  - Joey's Awakening: New Life (Parts 1,7,9,10,19,20), Joe Webster, 2000-2002; cuid24546 (Box 23, Folder 33)
  - Jogger Feeds On My 9 (Parts 1, 2), Muslickstud4u, 2001; cuid24547 (Box 23, Folder 34)
  - John and My Dad, CoolBlue35, 2003; cuid24548 (Box 23, Folder 35)
  - Johnny, Joni, and Chad, Maipenraikhap, 1999, cuid24549 (Box 23, Folder 36)
  - Johnny's Boi; My Thanksgiving Dinner; A Night to Remember, Loopy; PIG; Toilet Mike, 2000; cuid24550 (Box 23, Folder 37)
  - Jose, the Puerto Rican Shitter, Rich Dick, Undated; cuid24551 (Box 23, Folder 38)
  - Josh's Story, agrk3yotop, 1998, cuid24552 (Box 23, Folder 39)
  - Journal of a Pervert, Bawdypen, 2000, cuid24553 (Box 23, Folder 40)
  - The Journey (Part 3, 5, 6), Rim4You, 1996-2000; cuid24554 (Box 23, Folder 41)
  - The Judge's Disposition, Roderick Shafton, 2000, cuid24555 (Box 23, Folder 42)
  - Just for Fun, Joe Law, 1999, cuid24556 (Box 23, Folder 43)
  - Keith, Manager, Adult Books, David L. Hass, 2000, cuid24557 (Box 23, Folder 44)
  - Kelly's Toilet, loopy, Undated; cuid24558 (Box 23, Folder 45)
  - The Kid Bastards In Bunkhouse 40 (Chapter 5), Jeff Kincaid, Undated; cuid24559 (Box 23, Folder 46)
  - Kidnap!, A1 Writer, Undated; cuid24560 (Box 23, Folder 47)
  - Kip's Letter (Number 3-5, 8), Kip Ketter, 2000, cuid24561 (Box 23, Folder 48)
  - Kips Letter: The Last Letter, Maipenraikhap, 2000, cuid24562 (Box 23, Folder 49)
  - Laborer's Apprentice, Manny, 2000, cuid24563 (Box 23, Folder 50)
  - Latin Lover, Spa, David L. Hass, 2000, cuid24564 (Box 23, Folder 51)
  - Latin Lust, Up Arrow, Undated; cuid24565 (Box 23, Folder 52)
  - The Latrine, Leather Man, 1995, cuid24566 (Box 23, Folder 53)
  - Latrine Duty, Rim4you, 2000; cuid24567 (Box 23, Folder 54)
  - LeaDR House (Chapter 6-7), Theo North, Undated; cuid24568 (Box 23, Folder 55)
  - Leather Master, Rimpigfl, 1999, cuid24569 (Box 23, Folder 56)
  - Liberty (Parts 5,8,9), Doug Gage, Undated; cuid24570 (Box 23, Folder 57)
  - Lifestyles BBS: Connecticut's Premier Hot Spot, Beardlover, Undated; cuid24571 (Box 23, Folder 58)
  - Like Father Like Son, Moist Dreams, 1999, cuid24572 (Box 23, Folder 59)
  - Like Father, Like Sons (Parts 1-3), RC61Austin, 1999, cuid24573 (Box 23, Folder 60)
  - Little Boys At Old Charlie's Place, Xwriter, 2002, cuid24574 (Box 23, Folder 61)
  - A Little R&R, Rim4You, 2000; cuid24575 (Box 23, Folder 62)
  - The Little Stud, RimPig, 2002, cuid24576 (Box 23, Folder 63)
  - Live for Today, Devil Dog, 2000, cuid24577 (Box 23, Folder 64)
  - The Load Master, Wizzo, 2000; cuid24578 (Box 23, Folder 65)
  - Locker Room, Matti, 2003, cuid24579 (Box 23, Folder 66)
  - Locker Room Fun, Unknown, Undated; cuid24580 (Box 23, Folder 67)
  - Locker Room Meeting, Juergn Eichemueller, 1999, cuid24581 (Box 23, Folder 68)
  - Locker Room Shower Stud, Phineas Narco, 1998, cuid24582 (Box 23, Folder 69)
  - Lockerroom Shower Studs, Unknown, Undated; cuid24583 (Box 23, Folder 70)
  - Lockeroom Stink (Parts 1,3,5) Rim4You, 2001; cuid24584 (Box 23, Folder 71)
  - The Logger, Da Copper, 1998, cuid24585 (Box 23, Folder 72)
  - Loggerfuck, Furr, 1998, cuid24586 (Box 23, Folder 73)
  - Look At That Dickhead! (Cont.), 3u7d8, 2002; cuid24587 (Box 23, Folder 74)
  - Lost In Lust, Devil Dog, 2000, cuid24588 (Box 23, Folder 75)
  - Lovers, Nathan Harvey, 1999, cuid24589 (Box 23, Folder 76)
  - Lovers Dad, Bill Drake, 1999, cuid24590 (Box 23, Folder 77)
  - The Lubejob, An147051, 1994; cuid24591 (Box 23, Folder 78)
  - The Lucky Charm (Parts 1-4), Little Bad, 1997, cuid24592 (Box 23, Folder 79)
  - M2M Archive, man2man, 1996, cuid24593 (Box 23, Folder 80)
  - Mac Stevens and the Ten Loads (Parts 1-3), Cooper Smith, 2000, cuid24594 (Box 23, Folder 81)
  - Mac Stevens BBQ (Parts 1-3), Cooper Smith, 2000, cuid24595 (Box 23, Folder 82)
  - Mac Stevens: While the Cat's Away (Parts 1-3), Cooper Smith, 2001, cuid24596 (Box 23, Folder 83)
  - Mac's Frustrating Day (Part 2), PoliceFan36,1999; Mac's Frustrating Night, PoliceFan36, cuid24597 (Box 23, Folder 84)
  - The Mailman Delivers, Chadd Lusst, 1998, cuid24598 (Box 23, Folder 85)
  - The Maintenance Man and the Tearoom, Furr, Undated; cuid24599 (Box 23, Folder 86)
  - Making A Man of Me; Cleanin' Up Daddy, Mikeyeddie; Sandiego, 2000; cuid24600 (Box 23, Folder 87)
  - Making a Man of Me; Party Boy, Mike, EK, 2000, cuid24601 (Box 23, Folder 88)
  - Making Deliveries (Book 4- Part 1), Slick, 1997; cuid24602 (Box 23, Folder 89)
  - Making Deliveries, Slick, 2001, cuid24603 (Box 23, Folder 90)
  - Making of a Shit-Eater, Romacub, 2001, cuid24604 (Box 23, Folder 91)
  - Malt Liquor Drinker, K. Meacy, 2000, cuid24605 (Box 23, Folder 92)
  - The Man Down the Hall, Roderick Shafton, 2000, cuid24606 (Box 23, Folder 93)
  - Manolo Returns, Arablover, Undated; cuid24607 (Box 23, Folder 94)
  - Marine Capture, bushypits, 2000, cuid24608 (Box 23, Folder 95)
  - Marine Latrine (Part 1), Marc, 2002, cuid24609 (Box 23, Folder 96)
  - Marine Playtime, h_daze, 1999, cuid24610 (Box 23, Folder 97)
  - Marine Training (Parts 1 - 3), Etienne, 1996; cuid24611 (Box 23, Folder 98)
  - A Marine's Fantasy, Devil Dog, 2000; cuid24612 (Box 23, Folder 99)
  - A Marine's Slave Training - Part 1: Rebellion, Biker, Undated; cuid24613 (Box 23, Folder 100)
  - A Marine's Story (Part 2), Rimpigfl, 1999, cuid24614 (Box 23, Folder 101)
  - Mark's Uncle (Part 1), Unknown, Undated; cuid24615 (Box 23, Folder 102)
  - Matt Snaps His Fingers, loopy, 1998, cuid24616 (Box 23, Folder 103)
  - Max Stevens and Sgt Straight (Part 6), Cooper, 2000, cuid24617 (Box 23, Folder 104)
  - Me, Dad and Jacob (Parts 1, 2), Fleetwood, 2001, cuid24618 (Box 23, Folder 105)
  - Men At Work, Unknown, Undated; cuid24619 (Box 23, Folder 106)
  - Menage A Todd, PlowBoyOH, 1998; cuid24620 (Box 23, Folder 107)
  - The Men's Room (Parts 1-3), Rim4you, 2000; cuid24621 (Box 23, Folder 108)
  - The Michael Tapes (Parts 1-4), Marc Tremaine, 2000; cuid24622 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Mid-South Mess, Scott Baker, Undated; cuid24623 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Midnight In the Garden of Lust, Joe Wilson, Undated; cuid24624 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Midwest Raunch, An129138, 1995; cuid24625 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Miguel, noone, 1996, cuid24626 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Mike Gets His Boy, Black Flag, 2002, cuid24627 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Mike - Story of a Marine, Rimpigfl, 1999, cuid24628 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Military Dad, IncstBoy, Undated; cuid24629 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Military Madness (Parts 1-3), Bawdy Pen, 2000, cuid24630 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - The Milk Bar (Parts 1-7, 13), white collar, 2000, cuid24631 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Milking Cowboy, Rim4you, 2001; cuid24632 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - The Milkman (Parts 1-3), Glaucon55, 2000; cuid24633 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - More Family Fun; Family Fun-Forever, Balsam8, 1999; cuid24634 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - The Most Disturbing Behavior, loopy, Undated; cuid24635 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Motel (Parts 1-6), Joe Law, 2000, cuid24636 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Mountain Men (Part 3), Roderick Shafton, 2001, cuid24637 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Mountain Men (Muscle Bear), Myoder, 1996, cuid24638 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Mr. Black and Carlos (Part 2), dale10, 1999; cuid24639 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Mr. Black and Carlos (Parts 3 -6), Vic Collins, 2001, cuid24640 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Mr. Black and Danny, Dale10, 1999, 2001; cuid24641 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Mr. Black and the FBI (Parts 3,4,7,9,10,11,18), Dale10, 2000; cuid24642 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Mr. Black Hits the Mark, Maipenraikhap, 2000, cuid24643 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Mr. Black in Las Vegas, Maipenraikhap, 2000, cuid24644 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Mr. Black's Family Fun, Dale10, 1999; cuid24645 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Mr. Black's Interview, Dale10, 1999; cuid24646 (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Mr. Black's New Year Bash, Maipenraikhap, 1999, cuid24647 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Mr. Black's Return, Vic Collins, Undated; cuid24648 (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - Mr. Black's Visit, maipenraikhap, 1999, cuid24649 (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - Muscles and Sweat (Parts 1-3), Vincent Hadley, 2001; cuid24650 (Box 24, Folder 29)
  - My Army Dad, Man45years, 1999, cuid24651 (Box 24, Folder 30)
  - My Awakening (Parts 3,4), Rim4you, 2000; cuid24652 (Box 24, Folder 31)
  - My Best Friend's Dad, Story Teller, 2000, cuid24653 (Box 24, Folder 32)
  - My Best Friend's Father (Parts 1-3), fernandobuddy2002, cuid24654 (Box 24, Folder 33)
  - My Big Brother (Part 1), Maipenraikhap, 2000, cuid24655 (Box 24, Folder 34)
  - My Black Construction Dad (Parts 1-3), Fleetwood, 2002; cuid24656 (Box 24, Folder 35)
  - My Black Neighbors II, Mike (Filemup), 2001; My Next Visit, Mike (Fillemup), cuid24657 (Box 24, Folder 36)
  - My Blind Date, Rocky, Undated; cuid24658 (Box 24, Folder 37)
  - My Boyfriend, Maipenraikhap, 1999, cuid24659 (Box 24, Folder 38)
  - My Boyfriend: After School, Dale10, 1999; cuid24660 (Box 24, Folder 39)
  - My Boyfriend: All In the Family & In the Morning, Dale10, 1999; cuid24661 (Box 24, Folder 40)
  - My Candyass Kinky Boys, JayKingHoff, 1997, cuid24662 (Box 24, Folder 41)
  - My Dad, the Marine II (Parts 3-5), Rimpigfl, 1999-2000; cuid24663 (Box 24, Folder 42)
  - My Dads a Horny Bastard (Parts 2-3), JasonsFury, 1998, cuid24664 (Box 24, Folder 43)
  - My Desert Storm Trooper, Question Mark, 1998, cuid24665 (Box 24, Folder 44)
  - My Dream II, Jon Hold, 2000; cuid24666 (Box 24, Folder 45)
  - My First Marine (Parts 1-3), Rimpigfl, 2000, cuid24667 (Box 24, Folder 46)
  - My First Time With a Hairy Daddy, Not My Last, Daddy's Boy, 1997; cuid24668 (Box 24, Folder 47)
  - My Friend Steve, Slick, 1997, cuid24669 (Box 24, Folder 48)
  - My Gardener, David L. Hass, 2000, cuid24670 (Box 24, Folder 49)
  - My Kinky Fantasy Brought to Life, Ezgoing, 2002, cuid24671 (Box 24, Folder 50)
  - My Life As A Whore (Part 9,10,15-18), Joe Webster, 2001; cuid24672 (Box 24, Folder 51)
  - My Master, My Son (Parts 3-7, 10), Dennis, 1999-2000; cuid24673 (Box 24, Folder 52)
  - My Military Carrer, Dick Hunter, 2001, cuid24674 (Box 24, Folder 53)
  - My Military Carreer: Parts 8 - 10, Gaybottom, 2001, cuid24675 (Box 24, Folder 54)
  - My Nasty Dad (Parts 1-3), Rim4you, 2000; cuid24676 (Box 24, Folder 55)
  - My New Life (Part 21- 24), Joe Webster, 2002-2003; cuid24677 (Box 24, Folder 56)
  - My Setter, CoachinDC, 2000, cuid24678 (Box 24, Folder 57)
  - My Shame (Part 9), Maipenraikhap, 2002, cuid24679 (Box 24, Folder 58)
  - My Son's First Cum, Pedman, 2000, cuid24680 (Box 24, Folder 59)
  - My Step-dad and Me, Dr. Good, Undated; cuid24681 (Box 24, Folder 60)
  - My Thoughts On Last Night, Unknown; Hand, Unknown; Campground Piss Fest, Unknown; The Sewer Plumbers, Unknown, 1998; cuid24682 (Box 24, Folder 61)
  - N.Y.P.D Slut, Outlaw, 2000, cuid24683 (Box 24, Folder 62)
  - The Nate Hunter Saga - Chapter 1: Jail Bikers, Jack Forester and Eric, 1996; cuid24684 (Box 24, Folder 63)
  - Navy Relief, Awrt96, 1996; cuid24685 (Box 24, Folder 64)
  - The Neighbor Owns Me, Imyours497, 2000; cuid24686 (Box 24, Folder 65)
  - Neighborhood Slut, Joe Law, 1999, cuid24687 (Box 24, Folder 66)
  - Net Connect (Hot Jock), Fred, 1996, cuid24688 (Box 24, Folder 67)
  - Netting a Fisherman, Willi Edwards, 1995, cuid24689 (Box 24, Folder 68)
  - The New Guy Upstairs, Palucca69, 2000, cuid24690 (Box 24, Folder 69)
  - New Piggy, Devil Di Angelo, 1999, cuid24691 (Box 24, Folder 70)
  - New Piggy, Use_me27, Undated; cuid24692 (Box 24, Folder 71)
  - New Story for a Cop Botherer, copsucker 99, 2001; cuid24693 (Box 24, Folder 72)
  - Next Door Dog (Part 6), Pseudonym Station, 2000, cuid24694 (Box 24, Folder 73)
  - Nick's Big Pexs 4 (Chapters 1-7), Acepecs, 1998, cuid24695 (Box 24, Folder 74)
  - Night at the Brothel, joey1for, 1999, cuid24696 (Box 24, Folder 75)
  - Night At The Brothel, Luvtop, 1999; cuid24697 (Box 24, Folder 76)
  - Night Call, Bill Drake, 1999, cuid24698 (Box 24, Folder 77)
  - Night In the Woods, Creature, 1997, cuid24699 (Box 24, Folder 78)
  - A Night on the Road, Jake C, 2000, cuid24700 (Box 24, Folder 79)
  - Northern Woods Retreat III, WIWIWI, 2000; cuid24701 (Box 24, Folder 80)
  - Not Exactly, yourpighole, 2001, cuid24702 (Box 24, Folder 81)
  - Obsessed, Obsessed 4, Undated; cuid24703 (Box 24, Folder 82)
  - Obtuse Triangle, R. Keith Peck, 1997, cuid24704 (Box 24, Folder 83)
  - Odessa Ranch (Parts 1-3), Savagetrainer, 2000, cuid24705 (Box 24, Folder 84)
  - The Officer and the Quarterback, Bill Drake, 1999, cuid24706 (Box 24, Folder 85)
  - Officer Cole's Secret, glaucon55, 1998, cuid24707 (Box 24, Folder 86)
  - Officer's Boytoy, Unknown, Undated; cuid24708 (Box 24, Folder 87)
  - Oh Daddy My Daddy (Parts 3,5,6,7,8,10,11), K (I am K), 2000-2001; cuid24709 (Box 24, Folder 88)
  - Oh Yeah, Unknown, Undated; cuid24710 (Box 24, Folder 89)
  - Oil Rig, Richard Clark, 1996, cuid24711 (Box 24, Folder 90)
  - On the Range (Parts 1,5,7,8,11,12), Joe Law, 2000; cuid24712 (Box 24, Folder 91)
  - One Sunday Evening/Night, Sxuldev8, 2000; cuid24713 (Box 24, Folder 92)
  - One Wednesday Afternoon, Sxuldev8, 2000; cuid24714 (Box 24, Folder 93)
  - Open Up, Unknown, Undated; cuid24715 (Box 24, Folder 94)
  - Oral Rape: My Fantasy, Mickey (Daddy), 1999, cuid24716 (Box 24, Folder 95)
  - Orgy Boy, Roderick Shafton, 2000, cuid24717 (Box 24, Folder 96)
  - Our Italian Storekeeper 3, Fleetwood, 2001, cuid24718 (Box 24, Folder 97)
  - Out of Control (Part 2), Dogslife, 2001, cuid24719 (Box 24, Folder 98)
  - Paid in the Pitt, larry76712, 2003; cuid24720 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - The Paperboy, Dale10, 2000; cuid24721 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Parents Weekend (Chapters 1,5-8,10), billdrake, 2000; cuid24722 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Park Knights, JDL896, 2001; cuid24723 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Park Ranger, Michael D. Yoder, Undated; cuid24724 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Party at Pops? (Part 2,3,5,6), Unknown, 2001; cuid24725 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Paul's Posession, F150satx, 2000, cuid24726 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Peeking Into the Garage, Bawdy Pen, 2003, cuid24727 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Peeping Toms (Parts 1-3), Roderick Shafton, 2000; cuid24728 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - The Perils of Greggie-Poo: Episode 7, The Poem, ScatWoman, 1992; cuid24729 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Phone Repair, Douglascr, 1997, cuid24730 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Pickle Park Dilema, Truckhawk AKA Desertbear, Undated; cuid24731 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Pico, M, 1999; cuid24732 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - The Pig: At the Lakefront Festival, Dale10, 1999; cuid24733 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Pig for Cock, Devil Dog, 1999, cuid24734 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Pig Pit Stop, Tommy Bear, 2003, cuid24735 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Pig Slut (Chapter 1), Btmscott, 2001, cuid24736 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - The Pig: Visit to a Bookstore, Maipenraikhap, 2000; cuid24737 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Piglet, Blackflag, 2002, cuid24738 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Piss Fag, Unknown, Undated; cuid24739 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Piss Freak, Ron Kelly, 2002, cuid24740 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Piss Party in the Tearoom, JDL896, 2001; cuid24741 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Piss Slave, An70874, 1994; cuid24742 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - Pissy, Cagecashier, 1997, cuid24743 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Pit Stop, Nathan Harvey, 2000, cuid24744 (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - Play Pen Eight, Bob Archman, 2000, cuid24745 (Box 25, Folder 26)